{
    "question": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In the Homestuck Series, what is the alternate name for the Kingdom of Lights?",
            "correct_answer": "Prospit",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "No Name",
                "Golden City",
                "Yellow Moon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In 1978, Superman teamed up with what celebrity, to defeat an alien invasion?",
            "correct_answer": "Muhammad Ali",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mike Tyson",
                "Sylvester Stallone",
                "Arnold Schwarzenegger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "When was the Garfield comic first published?",
            "correct_answer": "1978",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "1982",
                "1973",
                "1988"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In what Homestuck Update was [S] Game Over released?",
            "correct_answer": "October 25th, 2014",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "April 13th, 2009",
                "April 8th, 2012",
                "August 28th, 2003"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "Which pulp hero made appearances in Hellboy and BPRD comics before getting his own spin-off?",
            "correct_answer": "Lobster Johnson",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Roger the Homunculus",
                "The Spider",
                "The Wendigo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "What are the names of the two &quot;Canon fan trolls&quot; in &quot;Homestuck&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Mierfa Durgas and Nektan Whelan",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Wrycrown and Voksea Olkido",
                "Aikter Frekik and Xagrai Ollomu",
                "Grekei Ceknux and Riya Camacho"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In the Batman comics, by what other name is the villain Dr. Jonathan Crane known?",
            "correct_answer": "Scarecrow",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Bane",
                "Calendar Man",
                "Clayface"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In the Marvel Universe, the planet of Svartalfheim is home to what race?",
            "correct_answer": "Dark Elves",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Frost Giants",
                "Kronans",
                "Skrulls"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "Better known by his nickname Logan, what is Wolverine&#039;s birth name?",
            "correct_answer": "James Howlett",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Logan Wolf",
                "Thomas Wilde",
                "John Savage"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "What year was the first San Diego Comic-Con?",
            "correct_answer": "1970",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "2000",
                "1990",
                "1985"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "What are the Three Virtues of Bionicle?",
            "correct_answer": "Unity, Duty, Destiny",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Build, Play, Change",
                "Work, Play, Live",
                "Forge, Build, Fight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In the webcomic &quot;Ava&#039;s Demon&quot;, what sin is &quot;Nevy Nervine&quot; based off of? ",
            "correct_answer": "Envy ",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Sloth",
                "Wrath ",
                "Lust"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In the &quot;Archie&quot; comics, who was Jughead&#039;s first girlfriend?",
            "correct_answer": "Joani",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Ethel",
                "Debbi",
                "Margret"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "What is the real hair colour of the mainstream comic book version (Earth-616) of Daredevil?",
            "correct_answer": "Blonde",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Auburn",
                "Brown",
                "Black"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "In the Hellboy universe, what was Abe Sapien&#039;s birth name?",
            "correct_answer": "Langdon Everett Caul",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lord Baltimore",
                "Sir Edward Grey",
                "Landis Pope"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "When Batman trolls the online chat rooms, what alias does he use?",
            "correct_answer": "JonDoe297",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "iAmBatman",
                "BWayne13",
                "BW1129"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
            "question": "Which of the following rings from the DC Comics&#039; &quot;Lantern Corps&quot; are classified as Parasitic?",
            "correct_answer": "Indigo (Compassion)",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Green (Willpower)",
                "White (Life)",
                "Yellow (Fear)"
            ]
        }
    ]
}